{
    "subject": "resource/Andrew_Jackson_Montague",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Richmond",
    "human_readable": "Andrew Jackson Montague attended University of Richmond.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873021841049194,
            "question": "Was Andrew Jackson Montague a student at University of Richmond?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9862926006317139,
            "question": "Did Andrew Jackson Montague study at the University of Richmond?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9496766924858093,
            "question": "Name one university Andrew Jackson Montague attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9488711357116699,
            "question": "Where did Andrew Jackson Montague attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8920564651489258,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Andrew Jackson Montague attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8585485219955444,
            "question": "To which university did Andrew Jackson Montague go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8531731963157654,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution Andrew Jackson Montague attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8069813251495361,
            "question": "What university did Andrew Jackson Montague go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7860100865364075,
            "question": "Andrew Jackson Montague's education took place where?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7127999663352966,
            "question": "Is Andrew Jackson Montague a university graduate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrew Jackson Montague attended University of Richmond.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4076_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrew Jackson Montague's education took place where?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4076_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university did Andrew Jackson Montague go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4076_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the institution Andrew Jackson Montague attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4076_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4076_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n* The document `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4076/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt` mentions Andrew Jackson Montague attending Richmond College (predecessor to the University of Richmond) in the following sentence:\n\" After his father died in 1880, Montague left the farm and went to Richmond, Virginia. He attended Richmond College (predecessor to the University of Richmond), where he gained a reputation as a skilled orator and debater.\"\n* This implies that Andrew Jackson Montague indeed attended the University of Richmond (as Richmond College is mentioned as its predecessor).\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Andrew Jackson Montague attended the University of Richmond, where he gained a reputation as a skilled orator and debater. Additionally, there is information indicating that he later served as the dean of its law school."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}